export const data = [
    
    {
    question: "What does this line of code do? \n css \n *{ \n box-sizing: border-box; \n }",
      option1: "It applies the code to all elements and ensures that padding and borders are included in the element's total width and height.",
      option2: "It applies the code to only div elements and helps fit content within the box by adjusting borders and padding.",
      option3: "It applies the code to everything and helps to fit the elements perfectly in box sizing by adjusting the border and padding to fit without extra math.",
      option4: "It applies the code to all elements except images and adjusts the margin and padding.", 
      ans: 3,
     },
     {
       question: "What does the viewport control?", 
       option1: "The total size of the webpage.", 
       option2: "The dimensions of the screen as viewed by the user.", 
       option3: "The size of text elements on the screen.", 
       option4: "The width of the borders on the screen.", 
       ans: 2, 
      },
      {
       question: "What are the viewport units for width and height?", 
       option1: "vw and vh", 
       option2: "vw and vhc",
        option3: "vh and vw", 
        option4: "vhc and vwc", 
        ans: 1, 
      },
      { 
        question: "Which CSS properties work with viewport units?", 
        option1: "padding; margin; border; height", 
        option2: "width; max-width; min-width; height", 
        option3: "color; background-color; border-radius; margin", 
        option4: "width; max-width; min-width; max-height",
        ans: 4, 
      },
      {
       question: "What are the 4 main value types of display properties and what do they do?",
       option1: "none, block, inline, inline-block", 
       option2: "flex, grid, block, inline", 
       option3: "none, flex, block, grid",
       option4: "block, inline, grid, flex", 
       ans: 1, 
      },
      { 
      question: "What is the default value for position properties?", 
      option1: "Absolute", 
      option2: "Fixed", 
      option3: "Static", 
      option4: "Relative", 
      ans: 3, 
      },
      {
       question: "What are the other value types of position properties and what do they do?", 
       option1: "Static, relative, fixed, flex", 
       option2: "Absolute, relative, fixed, sticky", 
       option3: "Block, inline, inline-block, none", 
       option4: "Grid, absolute, relative, sticky", 
       ans: 2, 
      },
      {
       question: "What is the z-index and when can it not be used?", 
       option1: "It determines the stacking order of elements and can't be used on relative position properties.", 
       option2: "It determines the stacking order of elements and can't be used on static position properties.", 
       option3: "It determines the stacking order of elements and can't be used on absolute position properties.", 
       option4: "It determines the stacking order of elements and can't be used on fixed position properties.", 
       ans: 2, 
      },
      { 
      question: "What is the default value for z-index and what are the rest?", 
      option1: "The default value is 1, and positive values move the element up, negative values move it down.", 
      option2: "The default value is 0, and positive values move the element up, negative values move it down.", 
      option3: "The default value is 1, and values above 10 move the element up, below 10 move it down.", 
      option4: "The default value is 0, and values between -10 and 10 determine the stack order.", 
      ans: 2, 
      },
      {
         question: "What does the float property allow you to do and how does it work?",
         option1: "It allows images to be centered on the page and works by setting the float value to center.", 
         option2: "It allows text to wrap around images and works by setting the float property inside an image selector.",
         option3: "It allows text to be justified and works by setting the float property to justify.", 
         option4: "It allows images to be aligned to the right and works by setting the float property inside a text selector.", 
         ans: 2,
         },
         {
         question: "What does a media query do and what are some types of rules?", 
         option1: "Media queries create rules based on the user's browser history.", 
         option2: "Media queries create rules based on device type and other characteristics like phone size and printing.", 
         option3: "Media queries create rules based on user input and screen resolution.", 
         option4: "Media queries create rules based on CSS version and HTML version.", 
         ans: 2, 
        },
        {
         question: "What does the box-shadow property do and how does it work?", 
         option1: "It creates shadows inside the box, and the syntax is box-shadow: inset x-axis y-axis blur rgbacolor().",
         option2: "It creates borders around the box, and the syntax is box-shadow: x-axis y-axis blur rgbacolor().", 
         option3: "It creates shadows outside the box, and the syntax is box-shadow: x-axis y-axis blur rgbacolor().", 
         option4: "It changes the background color of the box, and the syntax is box-shadow: x-axis y-axis blur rgbacolor().", 
         ans: 3,
         },
         {
         question: "What word would you need to add to create shadows inside the box?", 
         option1: "inner", 
         option2: "inset", 
         option3: "shadow", 
         option4: "inside", 
         ans: 2, 
        },
        {
         question: "What are the main properties used when defining fonts?", 
         option1: "font-family, font-size, font-weight, font-style, font-variant", 
         option2: "font-color, font-height, font-spacing, font-transform", 
         option3: "font-style, font-size, font-spacing, font-align", 
         option4: "font-family, font-height, font-width, font-style, font-color", 
         ans: 1, 
        },
         {
         question: "What are the main properties used when defining texts?", 
         option1: "color, line-height, letter-spacing, text-align, text-decoration, text-indent, text-transform", 
         option2: "color, text-height, letter-spacing, text-align, text-decoration, text-indent, text-shadow", 
         option3: "text-color, line-height, word-spacing, text-align, text-decoration, text-indent, text-transform", 
         option4: "font-color, text-height, letter-spacing, text-align, text-decoration, text-indent, text-shadow", 
         ans: 1, 
        },
        {
        question: "What does the border-radius property do?", 
        option1: "It creates circular borders for elements.", 
        option2: "It creates shadows around the element's borders.", 
        option3: "It creates rounded corners for elements.", 
        option4: "It creates gradients for the element's borders.", 
        ans: 3, 
      },
      {
       question: "Why is CSS reset used and what is a good example of it?", 
       option1: "To standardize all browsers to a default style and an example is normalize.css.", 
       option2: "To remove all built-in browser styling, leaving you to add all decorations yourself. An example is meyerweb.com reset.", 
       option3: "To enhance browser-specific styles and an example is bootstrap.css.", 
       option4: "To add additional styles to existing browser defaults and an example is normalize.css.", 
       ans: 2, 
      },
      {
       question: "Why is CSS normalize used and what is a good example of it?",
       option1: "To reduce browser inconsistencies and ensure consistent layout across all browsers. An example is normalize.css.", 
       option2: "To remove all built-in browser styling and ensure uniform layout. An example is meyerweb.com reset.", 
       option3: "To standardize web elements and ensure uniform appearance. An example is bootstrap.css.", 
       option4: "To enhance browser-specific features",
       ans: 1, 
      },
      {
       question: "What is mobile first and how does it work?", 
       option1: "It involves creating the desktop version first and then adding media queries for mobile.", 
       option2: "It involves creating the mobile version first and then adding media queries for larger screens.", 
       option3: "It involves creating the tablet version first and then adding media queries for mobile and desktop.", 
       option4: "It involves creating responsive designs for all devices simultaneously.", 
       ans: 2 
      },
    {
      question: "How does the clear property work in connection with the float property?",
      option1: "It removes all float properties from the image and text.",
      option2: "It clears the float property from the left side of the text only.", 
      option3: "It clears the text off the image either in the right, left, or both.", 
      option4: "It prevents text from wrapping around images completely.", 
      ans: 3, 
    },
    {
      question: "What is the last piece needed to use float properties correctly (besides clear) and what does it do?", 
      option1: "overflow; It prevents the container from wrapping around the image and text.", 
      option2: "overflow; It hides the image inside the container.", 
      option3: "clearfix; It creates a container that prevents the container from not wrapping around the image and text.", 
      option4: "display; It aligns the image and text inside the container.", 
      ans: 3,
     }
  ];